<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<packageId>kentington.saveourship2</packageId>
	<author>Kentington, Thain, SonicTHI</author>
	<name>Save Our Ship 2</name>
	<description>Save Our Ship 2 is an unofficial expansion for RimWorld. Build a liveable spaceship and continue your colonists' stories in orbit - engaging in ship-to-ship combat with pirates, searching derelicts for treasure, and perhaps even discovering a phenomenal cosmic secret or two! SoS2 includes two custom endings: build the Johnson-Tanaka drive to transport your colonists to a different rimworld for a New Game+ experience, or evolve one your colonists to machine godhood using the Archotech Spore.

Newly upgraded with tons of new features and stability upgrades for 1.5 and beyond, SOS2.7 is the best version of Save Our Ship yet.

SoS2's return would not have been possible without the tireless work of community volunteers. Featuring user-created ship designs, major community maintenance updates, and more, SoS2 owes thanks to:

2.7 Maintainer: Boris (Bqr1s on Github)

Testers: Dreamingofstarlight(Lunarium), I Forgot, Sym/Grimmy, Clever Ape, Dragoncri, Epoch_soc, Doubleface1369, Stylish, Splinter, TheGruntBox, Zeah

Submod Support: Ms Mommy Memner, I Forgot, Cruel Moose and thamuzz

Contributors: Boris, SonicTHI, Owlchemist, Oskar Potocki, Thamuzz1331, Trollam, K', Sarg, Karim, Saakra, Revolus, MatthewTeply, dkargin, HG, Morphium, Halno, Argón, DianaWinters, UrbanMonkey, M.A.G.Gen., Epicguru, sdanchenko, m00nl1ght-dev

Shipwrights: Oninnaise, VVither_Skeleton, (Insert Boi here), AlfadorZero, choppytehbear, Dammerung, Foxtrot, Inert, Jameson, Moonshine Dusk
		
OG Testing Squad: Buns Buns Cat, Phsarjk, i am has yes, Fuji, Reviire, Ian, Generic Scout, Waipa, Xanthos, BUTTERSKY, firethestars, Haldicar, jamhax, Jenden, maraworf, Red_Bunny, rostock, sprocket, El Jojo, Zahc, Dutchman, Zero Jackal, Tiberiumkyle, swordspell, Shabm, Kasodus, Red_Bunny, melandor, Madman, Jenden, Insert Witty Joke, Ifailatgaming, Capitão Escarlate, Bunkier, Bumblybear, Bubbadoge, Abraxas, Rage Nova, twsta, transcendant, thecaffiend, Manifold Paradox, WhiteGiverMa, Gago, Nerevarest</description>
	<url>https://github.com/KentHaeger/SaveOurShip2</url>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.0</li>
		<li>1.1</li>
		<li>1.2</li>
		<li>1.3</li>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</packageId>
			<displayName>Vehicle Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/3014915404</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/SmashPhil/Vehicles/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Anomaly</li>
		<li>SmashPhil.VehicleFramework</li>
		<li>oskarpotocki.vanillavehiclesexpandedtier3</li>
	</loadAfter>
	<incompatibleWith>
		<li>rwmt.multiplayer</li>
		<li>automatic.gunplay</li>
		<li>mlie.yayoscombat3</li>
		<li>majorhoff.rimthreaded</li>
		<li>user19990313777.runtimegc</li>
		<li>dhultgren.useminifiedbuildings</li>
		<li>impassablemapmaker.kv.rw</li>
		<li>lukakama.rimworldrealfow</li>
		<li>saakra.empire</li>
		<li>automatic.traderships</li>
		<li>vesper.egihologramsandprojectors</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.helixienGas</li>
		<li>vanillaexpanded.vee</li>
		<li>windowsxp.realisticplanets</li>
		<li>powerlunatic.flawlesselectronics</li>
		<li>limetreesnake.maintenance</li>
		<li>drzhivago.docworld</li>
		<li>storm.sos2ex</li>
	</incompatibleWith>
</ModMetaData>
